Guide to the Ronald Shiffman collection on the Pratt Center for Community Development 2013.023
Brooklyn Historical Society
- Series 4: Reports and Publications
  - Sub-series 4.1: Pratt Center
    - New York 2050, 1999-2003 (Box 60, Folder 10)
    - New York City's 312 Loan Program: A Preliminary Analyis, 1980 (Box 60, Folder 11)
    - Nominee for Whitney M. Yung Jr. Citation, 1988 (Box 60, Folder 12)
    - Opportunities for Low-Income Homeownership -- Frank DeGiovanni for Community Service Society, 1984 (Box 109, Folder 4)
    - Parks in New York City's Future, Third Annual Pratt Planning Conference, 1965 (Box 61, Folder 1-2)
    - Paul Davidoff, 1965-1984 (Box 61, Folder 3)
    - PCCI News in Brief Pratt Center for Community Improvement, 1967 (Box 70, Folder 18)
    - Peter Marcuse -- Pratt Planning Papers, 1965 (Box 61, Folder 4)
    - PICCED Clippings, 1987-1988 (Box 70, Folder 19)
    - PICCED Environment Posters, 1972 (Box 70, Folder 20)
    - PICCED in the News, 1987-1996 (Box 70, Folder 21)
    - PICCED Photographs, circa 1960-1975 (Box 70, Folder 22)
    - PICCED Plant Show and Sale, 1972 (Box 70, Folder 23)
    - PICCED Various Event Brochures, 1979-2000 (Box 71, Folder 1)
    - Planners Network, 1997-2002 (Box 71, Folder 2-4)
    - Planners Network c/o Pratt, 1995-1999 (Box 71, Folder 5)
    - Planning Profile #5 Magnolia Tree Tree Earth Center of Bed-Stuy. Inc., 1973 (Box 61, Folder 6)
    - Pratt Center and Ron Shiffman Related Articles, 1976-2015 (Box 71, Folder 6-10)
    - Pratt Center Clippings, 1966-1994 (Box 72, Folder 1)
    - Pratt Planning Papers, 1962-1963 (Box 72, Folder 4)
    - Pratt Planning Papers, 1965-1981 (Box 72, Folder 2-3)
      - PICCED Project Meeting Minutes, 1984-1985 (Box 61, Folder 5)
    - Pratt Center Internal Reports, 1981 (Box 61, Folder 7-8)
    - Preliminary Planning Analysis of the Brooklyn Atlantic Yards Project, 2005 (Box 61, Folder 9)
    - Proposal for the Essex Street Retail Market, 1986 (Box 61, Folder 10)
    - Public Parks, 1966-1969 (Box 61, Folder 11)
    - Rent-Regulated Multi-Family Housing Stock in Central Harlem, Bushwick, Ocean Hill-Brownsville, and Morris Heights, 1995 (Box 61, Folder 12)
    - Report of Operations, Community Education Program, 1963-1965 (Box 61, Folder 13)
    - Satellite Child Care System for Central Brooklyn, 1969 (Box 62, Folder 15)
    - Social Planning, 1965 (Box 63, Folder 5)
    - Social Planning -- Pratt Community Education Program, 1965 (Box 63, Folder 6)
    - Summary Project Status Reports, 1985 (Box 63, Folder 7)
    - Survey of South Bronx Organizations, 1979 (Box 63, Folder 8)
    - Sustainable Zoning, Undated (Box 63, Folder 9)
    - The Future of Low-Income Neighborhoods, Undated (Box 63, Folder 10)
    - Two Coves Community Redevelopment Council, 1994 (Box 63, Folder 11)
    - Two Coves Community Redevelopment Council, 1994 (Box 64, Folder 1)
    - W. Thabit Oral History, 1996-2007 (Box 64, Folder 2)
    - West Harlem and Greenpoint Newspapers, 1998, 2006 (Box 64, Folder 3)
  - Sub-series 4.2: Affiliated Organizations
    - The ASCA Sourcebook of Community Design Programs, 2000 (Box 73, Folder 4)
    - A Foundation to Build On: A Program to Revitalize New York City's Economy, 1990 (Box 64, Folder 4)
    - A Scan of Comprehensive Neighborhood Revitalization Programs -- New York Community Trust, 1993 (Box 64, Folder 5)
    - A Vision for the Hudson River Waterfront Park, 1990 (Box 64, Folder 6)
    - Advocacy and Pluralism in Planning Article -- Paul Davidoff for Symposium on Programming and the New Urban Planning, 1965 (Box 69, Folder 2)
    - Block by Block: Jane Jacobs and the Future of New York, 2007 (Box 64, Folder 7)
    - Brooklyn's Bridge to the Future: Strategic Plan for the Empowerment Zone, 1998 (Box 64, Folder 8)
    - Building Bridges: Community Development Corporations and the World of Employment Training, 1995 (Box 64, Folder 9)
    - Central Brooklyn Model Cities -- Office of the Mayor, 1969 (Box 64, Folder 10)
    - City Limits, 1981-1990 (Box 69, Folder 4-5)
    - City Limits Community Information Bulletin PICCED Housing Ed, 1972-1982 (Box 69, Folder 6)
    - City Limits -- The City Project, 1985-1988 (Box 73, Folder 5)
    - City Limits -- Integration: the Impossible Dream?, 1990 (Box 69, Folder 7)
    - Community Architectural Service Williamsburg, N.Y., 1970-1971 (Box 64, Folder 11)
    - The Community as Classroom: A Teacher's Manual, 1994 (Box 66, Folder 6)
    - Community Design Centers Profiles, 1975-1976 (Box 64, Folder 12)
    - Community Information Center Proposal, 1967 (Box 69, Folder 8)
    - Community Revitalization in the South Bronx: The Bronx Center, 1993 (Box 70, Folder 1)
    - Corrective Capitalism: The Rise of America's Community Development Corporations, 1987 (Box 64, Folder 13)
    - Creating Public Access to the Brooklyn Waterfront, 1990-1992 (Box 64, Folder 14)
    - Decentralizing Parks Services in New York City, 1975 (Box 70, Folder 2-3)
    - El Vedado pa' la gente, 2017 (Box 64, Folder 15)
    - Enhancing Vienna's Knowledge Culture, 1994 (Box 65, Folder 1)
    - Evidence Matters Publication, 2016 (Box 65, Folder 2)
    - Future of Camden City New Jersey Publication, 2001 (Box 70, Folder 5)
    - Governor's Island Land Use Study, 1997 (Box 65, Folder 3)
    - Holding Ground, Made in Brooklyn, and Squatters Documentaries, 1996 (Box 70, Folder 6)
    - HOME Program, Japan, 1993 (Box 70, Folder 7)
    - Household Diversity in Revitalizing Neighborhoods, 1984 (Box 116, Folder 9)
    - Housing Abandonment: Does Rent Control Make a Difference?, 1981 (Box 65, Folder 4)
    - Housing in the Balance: Seeking a Comprehensive Policy for City-Owned Housing, 1993 (Box 65, Folder 5)
    - Howard Golden Press Releases, 1996 (Box 70, Folder 8)
    - I.S. 201 Complex Community Information Manual, 1968-1969 (Box 65, Folder 6)
    - The Imperative of Deghettoization: An Answer to Piven and Cloward, 1967 (Box 73, Folder 6)
    - The Indigenous Times, 1995 (Box 73, Folder 7)
    - Integrating Housing and Welfare Assistance, 1987-1988 (Box 65, Folder 7)
    - Joel T. Werth and David Bryant -- A Guide to Neighborhood Planning, 1979 (Box 65, Folder 8)
    - The Local Official's Guide to the Community Reinvestment Act, 1990 (Box 66, Folder 7)
    - Los Sures Southside Housing Development Fund, Inc., 1972-1982 (Box 65, Folder 9)
    - The Los Sures Moderate Rehabilitation Study Committee, 1974 (Box 66, Folder 8)
    - Manufacturing Partnership of PICCED and NYIRN, 1994 (Box 70, Folder 10)
    - Methods of Urban Impact Analysis: Neighborhood Self-Help Development, 1978 (Box 65, Folder 10)
    - Metropolis Magazine, 2001-2002 (Box 70, Folder 11)
    - Miscellaneous News Clippings, 1994-1997 (Box 70, Folder 12)
    - Mississippi Action for Community Education -- The Delta Foundation, 1980 (Box 116, Folder 6)
    - MultipliCity Confronting Change -- Programs for Sustainable Planning and Development, 2015-2016 (Box 70, Folder 13)
    - Neighborhood Capacity Building: Part I, Technical and Management, 1983 (Box 70, Folder 14)
    - Neighborhood Development Newsletter -- American Planning Association Technical Division, 1981 (Box 70, Folder 15)
    - The Neighborhood Housing Movement, 1977 (Box 66, Folder 9)
    - Neighborhood Planning Primer, 1980 (Box 65, Folder 11)
    - News Clippings (Pratt), 1997 (Box 70, Folder 17)
    - The New York 2030 Notebook -- Institute for Urban Design, 2008 (Box 66, Folder 10)
    - The New York City In Rem Housing Program -- New York Urban Coalition, 1985 (Box 66, Folder 11)
    - New York Self Help Handbook -- Citizens Committee for New York City Inc, 1977 (Box 70, Folder 16)
    - New York Urban Coalition Annual Report and Program Plan, 1976-1977 (Box 65, Folder 13)
    - New York Urban Coalition Housing Rehabilitation Task Force, 1976 (Box 65, Folder 14)
    - New World Foundation Report on Community Self Help, 1980 (Box 65, Folder 12)
    - No Heat No Rent: An Urban Solar and Energy Conservation Manual, 1977 (Box 65, Folder 15)
    - Planning in a World City: New York and Its Communities, 1996 (Box 65, Folder 16)
    - Pratt Center Partners and Allies, 1971-1988 (Box 65, Folder 17-19)
    - Reforming the Community Development Program: the Key to Housing Rehabilitation, 1979 (Box 66, Folder 1)
    - Report of the Governor's Housing Task Force New York State Devember -- NYS Housing Task Force, 1988 (Box 66, Folder 2)
    - Roberta Gratz -- Miscellaneous, 1997-1999 (Box 72, Folder 6)
    - Roberta Gratz -- The Soho Syndrome, 1996 (Box 72, Folder 5)
    - Safe at Home: Yankee Stadium in the Bronx, 1998 (Box 66, Folder 3)
    - Small Retail Business Study Commission, 1986 (Box 66, Folder 4)
    - "Smart Growth" Built in Advantages Article in City Limits, 1999 (Box 69, Folder 1)
    - Still Off the Track: A Study of Subway Service -- NY Public Interest Research Center, Inc., 1983 (Box 66, Folder 5)
    - Street Housing Special, 1975-1976 (Box 72, Folder 7)
    - Street Magazine 1975 Special Charter Revision, 1975-1976 (Box 72, Folder 8)
    - Street Magazine of the Environment, 1972-1975 (Box 72, Folder 9-12)
    - Street Magazine of the Environment, 1972-1975 (Box 73, Folder 1-2)
    - Study of Housing Produced by Nonprofit Organizations, 1988 (Box 73, Folder 3)
    - Uprooting Poverty Through Community Development Article in City Limits, 1990 (Box 73, Folder 8)
    - Weeksville Then and Now, 1994 (Box 116, Folder 7)
    - Working Papers to Explore the Needs to Recognize and Support Initiative for Community Self-Help, 1980 (Box 73, Folder 9)
  - Sub-series 4.3: Foundations
    - A Manual for Hosting a Local Forum on Community-Based Development, 1988 (Box 66, Folder 12)
    - A Public-Private Venture to Revitalize the South Bronx, 1980 (Box 66, Folder 13)
    - A Report on the Blackout Looting, 1978 (Box 66, Folder 14)
    - Encouraging Stability, Peace and Justice in the International Order, 1987 (Box 66, Folder 15)
    - Famicos Foundation, 1981-1982 (Box 66, Folder 16)
    - Ford Foundation, 1994 (Box 67, Folder 1)
    - Ford Foundation and Other Grants, 1987-1988 (Box 67, Folder 2)
    - Ford Foundation and The Consumer-Farmer Cooperator, 1977-1987 (Box 67, Folder 3)
    - Ford Foundation Conference Papers, 1951-1985 (Box 67, Folder 4)
    - Ford Foundation PRI Loan, 1987 (Box 67, Folder 5)
    - Ford Foundation Urban Poverty Program, 1988-1989 (Box 67, Folder 6)
    - Ford Internship, 1991-1996 (Box 67, Folder 7)
    - Fund for the Improvement of Postsecondary Education, 1981-1984 (Box 67, Folder 8)
    - Fundraising Files, 1975-1993 (Box 67, Folder 9)
    - George Soros and the Cloverleaf Plan, 1994-1996 (Box 67, Folder 10)
    - Neighborhoood Land Disposition Plan: East New York/New Lots, 1992 (Box 67, Folder 11)
    - PICCED Miscellaneous Proposals, 1996 (Box 67, Folder 12)
    - Pratt Center Education Exchange -- Proposals, 1991-1996 (Box 67, Folder 13)
    - PRI Loan, 1987 (Box 67, Folder 14)
    - Program-Related Investments Review Paper, 1987 (Box 67, Folder 15)
    - Rockefeller Foundation Mohonk, 2002 (Box 68, Folder 1)
    - Rural Poverty and Resource Management, 1987 (Box 68, Folder 2)
    - Staff Conference on Urban Community Initiatives, 1989 (Box 68, Folder 3)
    - Support for Emerging Community Development Corporations, 1983 (Box 68, Folder 4)
    - The AIDS Challenge: A Ford Foundation Response, 1987 (Box 68, Folder 5)
    - The Education and Culture Program's Minority Teacher Education Program, 1988 (Box 68, Folder 6)
    - The Ford Foundation -- Leadership in Affecting Poverty, 1987 (Box 116, Folder 8)
    - The Ford Foundation Developing Country Programs, 1987 (Box 68, Folder 7)
    - The Ford Foundation Program on Education and Culture, 1987 (Box 68, Folder 8)
    - The Ford Foundation: Leadership in Affecting Poverty, 1987 (Box 68, Folder 9)
    - The Ford Foundation: Pluralism and Diversity, 1987 (Box 68, Folder 10)
    - The Potential for Program-Related Investments in the Ford Foundation's Developing Country Programs, 1987 (Box 68, Folder 11)
    - Urban Institutions Program Report and National Conference Proceedings, 1988 (Box 68, Folder 12)
    - Urban Poverty Program/Workshop for Emerging Community Development Corporations, 1984 (Box 68, Folder 13)
    - What Ever Happened to Poverty Alleviation?, 1987 (Box 68, Folder 14)
    - Women and Children in Poverty: Reproductive Health and Child Survival, 1987 (Box 68, Folder 15)
- Series 5: International Work
  During the 1990s and early 2000s, Shiffman and the Pratt Center undertook substantial international consulting work. The majority of this series reflects projects in South Africa and Europe. Materials pertaining to South Africa include affordable housing projects, the Rural Advice Center, community development initiatives, outreach and conferences, as well as the micro-granting organization Shared Interest. Materials reflecting European projects include a French tour and exchange, German collaborations, and the Salzburg Congress on Planning and Development. This series also contains materials about Chile, Israel, Russia, and Japan.
  - A Community-Based Development Strategy for South Africa -- US Agency for International Development, 1990 (Box 73, Folder 10)
  - Affordable Housing in Alexandria, South Africa and People's Express, 1990-1991 (Box 73, Folder 11)
  - Africa -- African Participant Profiles, 1991 (Box 73, Folder 12)
  - Africa -- African Participants, 1991 (Box 74, Folder 1)
  - Africa -- Conference Follow Up Thanks Received, 1991 (Box 74, Folder 2)
  - Africa -- Revised Addresses, 1991-1992 (Box 74, Folder 3)
  - Africa -- United States Participants, 1991 (Box 74, Folder 4)
  - Africa -- Workbook, 1991 (Box 74, Folder 5)
  - Africa Community Development Finance Conference Fall 1991, 1991-1992 (Box 73, Folder 13)
  - Africa Conference -- Participant Lists, 1991-1992 (Box 73, Folder 14-15)
  - African National Congress -- PICCED, 1991 (Box 74, Folder 6)
  - AHEC/Community Partners Russia Trip, 1996 (Box 74, Folder 7)
  - All National Fund (ANF) Russia, 1995-1996 (Box 74, Folder 8)
  - Buenos Aires Visit, 1997-1998 (Box 74, Folder 9)
  - Chile, 1993-1995 (Box 74, Folder 10)
  - Chile -- Coneulo Gazmuri's Paper, 1993 (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - Chile -- List of Participants in Chile Exchange, 1993 (Box 75, Folder 3)
  - Chile -- Trip to Chile July 1993 (Box 75, Folder 4)
  - Chile Exchange -- Material from Trip, 1993 (Box 74, Folder 11-12)
  - Chile Exchange -- Material from Trip, 1993 (Box 75, Folder 1)
  - Chile/US Exchange Logistics and Tour Arrangements, 1993 (Box 75, Folder 5-7)
  - Chile/Vergara/Ford, 1994-1996 (Box 75, Folder 8)
  - Community Development Finance in Africa Conference, 1991 (Box 75, Folder 9-10)
  - Community Development in Japan, 1995-1996 (Box 75, Folder 11)
  - Community Revitalization in Central Europe, 1991-2000 (Box 76, Folder 1)
  - COPE/CAST Cooperative Planning and Education, 1991 (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - CUNY Concept Paper on Internships for South Africa, 1991 (Box 76, Folder 3)
  - Czech Republic, 1996 (Box 76, Folder 4)
  - Draft Report to the Ford Foundation Development Finance March 1991 (Box 76, Folder 5)
  - Drug Treatment Alternative to Prison Housing Program (DTAP), 1993 (Box 76, Folder 6)
  - Edilter Construction Company, circa 1990s (Box 76, Folder 7)
  - Emscher Park Study Tour -- Admin, 1997 (Box 76, Folder 8)
  - England, 1993-1996 (Box 76, Folder 9)
  - Europe 2002 PICCED Europe Tour, 2002-2004 (Box 76, Folder 10)
  - European Delegation, 2002 (Box 76, Folder 11)
  - Evangelische Akademie Lokkum, 1992-1994 (Box 76, Folder 12)
  - Exchange European -- PICCED Visit Exchange, 2002 (Box 76, Folder 13)
  - Ford-Funded African Participants in Training Program 1991-92 (Box 76, Folder 14)
  - France and Vienna Visit, 1993 (Box 76, Folder 15)
  - France Exchange, 1992-1995 (Box 76, Folder 16-17)
  - France Exchange, 1992-1993 (Box 77, Folder 1)
  - France Exchange -- French Visit to the United States, 1993 (Box 77, Folder 2)
  - France Exchange -- French-American Foundation Tour, 1992 (Box 77, Folder 3)
  - France Exchange -- French-American Foundation Tour of France, 1992-1994 (Box 77, Folder 4)
  - France Visit December, 1993 (Box 77, Folder 5)
  - France Visit November, 1993 (Box 77, Folder 6)
  - Fred O'Regan's Evaluation of the Africa Conference, 1991-1992 (Box 77, Folder 7)
  - French Approaches to the Urban Crisis -- Ron Shiffman Delegate, 1992 (Box 77, Folder 8)
  - German Marshall Fund, 2002 (Box 77, Folder 9)
  - German Participants in the Red Hook Workshop, 1996 (Box 77, Folder 10)
  - Germany -- Emscher Park and Duisburg, 1994-1996 (Box 77, Folder 13-14)
  - Germany (IBA), 1992-1997 (Box 77, Folder 11-12)
  - Grassroots Action in a Global World Seminar, Pocantico, 2000 (Box 78, Folder 1)
  - Handouts from Africa Conference, 1991 (Box 78, Folder 2)
  - House Banking Committee -- NAFTA, 1993-1994 (Box 78, Folder 3)
  - Housing in the Netherlands, 1978-1983 (Box 78, Folder 4-5)
  - IBA Germany in Hamburg and Bitterfeld, 2000-2010 (Box 78, Folder 6)
  - Institute Trappetto, undated (Box 141, Item 424)
  - Interfaith Center on Corporate Responsibility ICCR SANCO, 1991-1995 (Box 78, Folder 7)
  - International Community Development Curriculum, 1991 (Box 78, Folder 8)
  - International Development, 1992-1995 (Box 78, Folder 9)
  - International Guarantee Fund, 1995-1996 (Box 78, Folder 10)
  - International Neighborhood South Africa Issues, 1982-1992 (Box 78, Folder 11-12)
  - International Projects, 1992-2008 (Box 79, Folder 1)
  - International Symposium 'Local Economy' Technical University of Berlin, 1992 (Box 79, Folder 2)
  - International Urban Development, 1980-2002 (Box 79, Folder 3-5)
    Contains 2 CDs
  - International Work, 1992-2002 (Box 79, Folder 6-7)
  - International Work Including Germany, UNICEF, and South Africa, 1989-1995 (Box 79, Folder 8)
  - Investing in People Conference on South Africa, 1994 (Box 79, Folder 9)
  - IRED Innovations et Reseaux pour le Developpement / Development Innovations and Networks, 1993-1999 (Box 79, Folder 10-11)
  - IRED Innovations et Reseaux pour le Developpement / Development Innovations and Networks, 1993-1999 (Box 80, Folder 1-8)
  - IRED Innovations et Reseaux pour le Developpement / Development Innovations and Networks, 1993-1999 (Box 81, Folder 1)
  - IRED Innovations et Reseaux pour le Developpement / Development Innovations and Networks -- Rome, Italy, 1994 (Box 81, Folder 3)
  - IRED International, 1992-1994 (Box 81, Folder 2)
  - Israel, 1996-1997 (Box 81, Folder 4)
  - Johannesburg Housing Corporation Inner City Housing Design, 1997 (Box 81, Folder 5)
  - Joint UHAB proposal to USAID Russia, 1994-1995 (Box 81, Folder 6)
  - Kellogg Educational Development for Development Staff, 1991 (Box 81, Folder 7)
  - L'Espoir, 1996 (Box 140, Item 471)
    VHS NTSC SUBMASTER 525/60. Runtime: 0:52:00
  - Margins of the City Symposium on Local Communities in Global Restructuring, 1993-1994 (Box 81, Folder 8)
  - Mega-Cities -- Innovations for Urban Life, 1993 (Box 81, Folder 9)
  - Ministerium fur Stadtentwicklung, Kultur, and Sport des Landes, 1998-2001 (Box 81, Folder 10)
  - Mzwanele Mayekizo -- Planner's Network Article, 1995 (Box 81, Folder 11)
  - Neighborhood Economic Development Seminar, 1979-1980 (Box 81, Folder 12)
  - New York City Commission on Human Rights Triville, France Conference, 1991 (Box 81, Folder 13)
  - Originals International Projects, Ford Foundation, 1991-1992 (Box 81, Folder 14)
  - Parks Council -- Miscellaneous, 1994-1996 (Box 85, Folder 12)
  - Peace Dividend Network, 1990 (Box 81, Folder 15)
  - Personnel New York City, 1990-1991 (Box 82, Folder 1)
  - Planact South Africa, 1989-1991 (Box 82, Folder 2-5)
  - Pratt Center Visitors -- South Africa, 1995-1996 (Box 82, Folder 6)
  - Pratt Institute -- City of Duisbury, 1998 (Box 142, Item 411)
    VHS NTSC Submaster. Runtime: 0:15:03
  - Pratt Institute L'Espoir, 1996 (Box 138, Item 316)
    VHS NTSC Submaster 525/60. Runtime: 0:50:46
  - Pratt Institute, Bottrop, Uberraschend Anders, 1998 (Box 142, Item 412)
    VHS NTSC Submaster 525/60. Runtime: 0:15:30
  - Prefeitura do Municipio de Sao Paul Secretaria Municipal do Planejamento, 1996 (Box 82, Folder 7)
  - Proposal South Africa, 1990 (Box 82, Folder 8)
  - RAFAD Research and Applications of Alternative Financing for Development, 1985-1995 (Box 82, Folder 9)
  - Roberta Gratz/Vankovka, 2000-2001 (Box 82, Folder 10)
  - Rome-South Africa Project, 1990 (Box 85, Folder 13)
  - Ron -- Europe Commentaries, 2002 (Box 82, Folder 11)
  - Ron's European Visitors to PICCED, 2002 (Box 82, Folder 12)
  - Rotterdam Trip, 1997 (Box 82, Folder 13)
  - Rudy's Trip to India, 1995 (Box 82, Folder 14)
  - Rural Advice, 1990-1991 (Box 82, Folder 15)
  - Rural Advice Center, 1990-1991 (Box 83, Folder 1)
  - Rural Advice Center -- South Africa Conference, 1990-1991 (Box 83, Folder 2)
  - Russia ANF, 1991-1996 (Box 83, Folder 3-6)
  - Salzburg Congress, 1984 (Box 83, Folder 7)
  - Salzburg Congress on Urban Planning and Development, 1991-1992 (Box 83, Folder 8)
  - Salzburg Congress on Urban Planning and Development, 1997-1998 (Box 83, Folder 9)
  - Soche Progressive Institute of Education, 1996 (Box 83, Folder 10)
  - Society for International Development Sustainable Livelihoods Programme, 1996 (Box 83, Folder 11)
  - South Africa, 1989-1997 (Box 83, Folder 12-14)
  - South Africa, 1989-1997 (Box 84, Folder 1-5)
  - South Africa, 1989 (Box 85, Folder 1)
  - South Africa Congressional, 1988-1989 (Box 84, Folder 6-8)
  - South Africa Notes, Clippings, and Papers, 1991-1993 (Box 84, Folder 9)
  - South Africa Notes, Clippings, and Papers, 1984-1990 (Box 85, Folder 2-3)
  - South Africa Post-Graduate Public Policy and Development Administration Programme, 1991 (Box 85, Folder 4)
  - South Africa Shared Interest, 1996 (Box 85, Folder 5)
  - South Africa USAID Mott Ford, 1989-2002 (Box 85, Folder 6-8)
  - South Africa USAID Mott Ford -- South African Rural Development Support Program, 1992-1993 (Box 85, Folder 9)
  - South African Outreach Effort, 1991 (Box 85, Folder 10)
  - SUNY-Brooklyn -- Outreach Programs, 1989 (Box 85, Folder 11)
  - Tender for Acquisition of a Share in Reconstruction Investment (Moscow, Russia, 1/2 Solyanka Street), 1995 (Box 138, Item 360)
  - Tender for Acquisition of a Share in Reconstruction Investment (Moscow, Russia, 1/2 Solyanka Street), November 3, 1995 (Box 138, Item 361)
    VHS. Runtime: 0:04:45
  - Tender for Acquisition of a Share in Reconstruction Investment (Moscow, Russia, 1/2 Solyanka Street), September 25, 1995 (Box 138, Item 364)
    VHS NTSC SUBMASTER 525/60. Runtime: 0:04:45
  - Tender for Acquisition of a Share in Reconstruction Investment (Moscow, Russia, 1/2 Solyanka Street), September 25, 1995 (Box 138, Item 365)
  - Tender for Acquisition of a Share in Reconstruction Investment (Moscow, Russia, 1/2 Solyanka Street), 1995 (Box 142, Item 413)
  - Transcultural Practices in Architecture and Urbanism, 2015 (Box 85, Folder 14)
  - Travel -- PICCED Europe Tour, 2002 (Box 85, Folder 15)
  - UNICEF Urban Consulation, 1992-1993 (Box 86, Folder 1)
  - United Nation, 1993-1997 (Box 86, Folder 2)
  - United Nations Cuban Delegation Reception and Seminar Puck Building, February 9, 1996 (Box 142, Item 447)
  - Urban Assembly, 1991-1997 (Box 86, Folder 3-4)
  - Urban Strategies -- The Rene Dubos Center for Human Environments Inc., 1989 (Box 86, Folder 5)
  - Urban Summit Conference, 1989-1990 (Box 86, Folder 6-7)
  - VCDO Magazine 2, undated (Box 142, Item 451)
  - VIMAR -- Vivienda Para Los Marginados, 1987-1989 (Box 86, Folder 8)
  - Voices from South Africa American Friends Service Conference Part 2, undated (Box 138, Item 312)
    VHS. Runtime: 0:26:00
  - World Bank, 1992-1999 (Box 86, Folder 9)
  - Zu Neuen Ufern, 1998 (Box 138, Item 366)
    VHS NTSC SUBMASTER 525/60. Runtime: 0:16:03
- Series 6: Housing Developments and Architectural Projects